Contact

chimato2012@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/chima-egwim-bsn-rn-cmsrn-7b98b871 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills
CPR Certified
Healthcare Management
HIPAA

Chima Egwim, BSN,RN,CMSRN

Clinical Nurse at Health+Trust (HEALTHPLUSTRUST)
Houston, Texas Area

Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Customer Service, Microsoft Word, Cardiopulmonary Resuscitation (CPR), U.S. Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act (HIPAA), and Microsoft Office. Strong healthcare services professional with a Bachelor's degree in nursing focused in Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse from Prairie View A&M University.

Experience

Health+Trust (HEALTHPLUSTRUST)
Clinical Nurse
January 2016 - Present (4 years 7 months)
Houston, Texas Area

The University of Texas MD Anderson Cancer Center Clinical Nurse 2014 - Present (6 years)

Education

Prairie View A&M University
Bachelor's degree in nursing, Registered Nursing/Registered
Nurse · (2011 - 2013)

Austin Community College (2007 - 2010)